Finding Aid for Provost and Executive Vice-President for Academic Affairs (University of Michigan) Central Files
Bentley Historical Library
- Central Files
  - 1983-1984
    - Alphabetical Files
      - Executive Officers
        - Officers
          - Vice Presidents
            - Frye, Bill E. (Academic Affairs) (includes personal), 2 folders (Box 158)
            - Johnson, Harold (Student Services) (Box 158)
            - Kennedy, Richard L. (State Relations) (Box 158)
            - Sussman, Alfred S. (Graduate Studies and Research) (Box 158)
      - Extension Service (Box 159)
      - Faculty Appointments (Box 303)
      - Faculty Unionization (Box 303)
      - Fees and Tuition (Box 159)
      - Financial Aid, Office of
        - General (Box 159)
        - Draft Registration (Box 159)
        - Task Force on Undergraduate Student Aid (Box 159)
      - Foundations (Box 159)
      - Gender Studies (Box 159)
      - Government Agencies (Box 159)
      - Graduate Student Assistants (GSA's) (Box 159)
      - Grievance Procedures (Box 159)
      - Grievances (Box 303)
      - Honorary Degrees (Box 159)
      - Hospital
        - General (Box 159)
        - Breakfast Meetings, 3 folders (Box 159)
        - Executive Board (Box 159)
        - Financing (Box 159)
        - Governance (Box 160)
        - Joint Conference Committee (Box 160)
        - Long Range Planning (Box 160)
        - Medical Science Plan (Box 160)
        - Replacement Hospital Project (Box 160)
      - Housing Office (Box 160)
      - Humor (Box 160)
      - Indirect Cost Reimbursement (Box 160)
      - Industry (Box 160)
      - Institute for Public Policy Studies (IPPS) (Box 160)
      - Institute for Science and Technology (IST) (Box 160)
      - Institute for Social Research (ISR) (Box 160)
      - Institute of Gerontology (IOG) (Box 160)
      - Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations (ILIR) (Box 160)
      - International (Box 160)
      - Investments (Box 160)
      - Invitations (Box 160)
      - Lansing Offices (Box 160)
      - Libraries
        - Bentley Historical Library (Box 160)
        - Clements Library (Box 160)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 160)
        - University Library
          - General (Box 161)
          - Budget Conference (Box 161)
      - Management Intercom (Box 161)
      - Memberships (Box 161)
      - Michigan Media (Box 161)
      - Michigan Research Corp (Box 161)
      - Michigan Union (budget) (Box 161)
      - Minorities (Box 161)
      - Minority Student Recruitment/Retention Task Force (Box 161)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 161)
      - Museum of Art (Box 161)
      - National Student Exchange/National Faculty Exchange (Box 161)
      - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (NASULGC) (Box 161)
      - News and Information Services (Box 161)
        (see University of Michigan News and Information Services)
      - Personnel (C. Allmand) (Box 161)
      - Plant Operations Review Committee (Box 162)
      - Policies and Procedures (Box 162)
      - Postdoctoral Fellow Committee (Box 162)
      - Professional Theatre Program (PTP) (Box 162)
      - Promotions (Box 162)
      - Recommendation, Letters of (Box 162)
      - Regents
        - General (Box 162)
        - Bylaws (Box 162)
        - Communications (Box 162)
        - Correspondence (Box 162)
        - Fellowship (Box 162)
      - Registrar's Office (Box 162)
      - Reproductive Endocrinology Program (Box 162)
      - Research Ethics (Box 162)
      - Research/Rackham Merger (merger of Offices of Vice President for Research and Dean of Rackham School of Graduate Studies) (Box 162)
      - Reserve Officer Training Corps (ROTC) (Box 162)
      - Retirement Furlough (Box 162)
      - Retrenchment Materials (Box 162)
      - Salary Information (Box 162)
      - Salary Recommendations (Box 303)
      - Scholarships and Fellowships (Box 163)
      - Scholarships, Integrity of (Box 163)
      - Scientific Club (Box 163)
      - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA) (Box 163)
      - Senate Assembly (Box 163)
      - Separate Legal Entity (Box 163)
      - Software Engineering Institute (Box 163)
      - Society of Fellows (Box 163)
      - SOUP Group (Box 163)
      - South Africa (Box 163)
      - Space and Equipment (Box 163)
      - Staff Records Office (Box 163)
      - Students (Box 163)
      - Telecommunications (Box 163)
      - Tenure (Box 163)
      - Transmission Link, Microwave (Flint) (Box 163)
      - University of Michigan News and Information Services (Box 163)
      - University Record (Box 163)
      - Villa Information (Box 163)
      - Visits (Box 163)
      - Wang Alliance (Box 163)
      - Wayne County General Hospital (Box 163)
      - Women (Box 163)
    - Schools and Colleges
      - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of
        - General (Box 164)
        - Budget Conference (Box 164)
        - Dean Evaluation (Box 303)
      - Art, School of
        - General (Box 164)
        - Budget Conference (Box 164)
        - Review, 2 folders (Box 164)
        - Transition Team (Box 164)
      - Business Administration, School of, 2 folders (Box 164)
      - Dearborn Campus (Box 164)
      - Dentistry, School of
        - General (Box 164)
        - Budget Conference (Box 164)
      - Education, School of
        - General, 3 folders (Box 164)
        - Budget Conference (Box 165)
        - Dean Search (Box 303)
        - Review, 7 folders (Box 165)
        - Teacher Education, 2 folders (Box 165)
        - Transition Team, 2 folders (Box 165)
      - Engineering, College of
        - General, 6 folders (Box 166)
        - Budget Conference, 6 folders (Box 166)
        - Building (Box 167)
        - Center for Robotics and Integrated Manufacturing (CRIM) (Box 167)
        - Computers (Box 167)
        - Department of Humanities Review (Box 167)
        - General Motors Institute (GMI) (Box 167)
        - North Campus Move (Box 167)
      - Flint Campus (Box 167)
      - Graduate Studies, Rackham School of, 2 folders (Box 167)
      - Law School
        - General (Box 167)
        - Budget Conference (Box 167)
      - Library Science, School of
        - General (Box 167)
        - Budget Conference (Box 167)
      - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of
        - Appointments, Promotions and Recruitment (Box 303)
        - Budget Conference (Box 167)
        - Chemistry (Box 167)
        - Classical Studies (Box 167)
        - Coalition for the Use of Learning Skills (CULS) and Opportunity Program (Box 167)
        - Collegiate Institute for Values and Science (CIVS) (Box 167)
        - Communications (Box 167)
        - Computer and Communication Sciences (Box 167)
        - Dean Peter O. Steiner (Box 168)
        - Economics (Box 168)
        - Electrical and Computer Engineering and Computer and Communication Science Merger (Box 168)
        - Endowments/Fellowships (Box 168)
        - English (Box 168)
        - English Composition Board (ECB) (Box 168)
        - Geological Sciences (Box 168)
        - History (Box 168)
        - History of Art (Box 168)
        - Humanities (Box 168)
        - Mathematics (Box 168)
        - Miscellaneous Units, 2 folders (Box 168)
        - Museums and Centers (Box 168)
        - Natural Science Building Renovation (Box 168)
        - Near Eastern Studies (Box 168)
        - Philosophy (Box 168)
        - Physics (Box 168)
        - Political Science (Box 168)
        - Psychology (Box 168)
        - Psychology/Education (Box 168)
        - Sociology (Box 168)
        - Thurnau, Arthur F. Estate (Box 168)
      - Medical Affairs, Vice Provost For
        - General (Box 169)
        - Search (Box 303)
      - Medical School
        - General, 3 folders (Box 303)
        - Appointments, Promotions and Recruitment, 1 folder (Box 303)
        - Budget Conference (Box 169)
        - Bequests (Box 169)
        - Biomedical Research (Box 169)
        - Burn Center (Box 169)
        - Enrollment (Box 169)
        - Inteflex Program (Box 169)
        - Medical Education Task Force (Box 169)
        - Medical Science Building (Box 169)
        - Medical Service Plan Office (Box 170)
        - Medical Technology Program (Box 170)
      - Music, School of
        - General (Box 170)
        - Budget Conference (Box 170)
        - Department of Theatre
          - General (Box 170)
          - Review (Box 170)
      - Natural Resources, School of
        - General (Box 170)
        - Budget Conference (Box 170)
        - Review (Box 170)
        - Transition Team (Box 170)
      - Nursing, School of
        - General (Box 170)
        - Budget (Box 170)
      - Pharmacy, School of
        - General (Box 170)
        - Budget (Box 170)
      - Physical Education, 3 folders (Box 171)
      - Public Health, School of
        - General (Box 171)
        - Budget Conference (Box 171)
        - Dean Search (Box 303)
      - Social Work
        - General (Box 169)
        - Budget Conference (Box 169)
        - Reaccreditation, 1 folder (two volumes) (Box 169)
  - 1984-1985
    - Alphabetical Files
      - Academic Affairs Advisory Council, 3 folders (Box 172)
      - Academic Affairs Assessment and Issues Identification (Box 172)
      - Academic Affairs Brown Bag Meetings (Box 172)
      - Academic Affairs Committee (Box 172)
      - Academic Affairs Current Account (Box 172)
      - Academic Affairs Evaluation (Box 172)
      - Academic Affairs Organization (Box 172)
      - Academic Affairs Staff (Box 172)
      - Academic Affairs Staff Meeting Agenda (Box 172)
      - Academic Affairs Status Report (Box 172)
      - Academic Planning and Analysis, Office of (Box 172)
      - Academic Records (Box 173)
      - Academic Service Units (Robert Holmes) (Box 173)
      - Administrative Systems Office (Box 173)
      - Admissions, Office of
        - General, 2 folders (Box 173)
        - Task Force (Box 173)
      - Affirmative Action Office (Box 173)
      - Alumni Association
        - General (Box 173)
        - Black Alumni Leadership Advisory Committee (Box 173)
      - American Council on Education (ACE) (Box 173)
      - Arms Control ( 2 folders) (Box 173)
      - Articles of Interest (Box 173)
      - Associate Vice Presidents
        - Holbrook, Robert S (Box 173)
        - Sudarkasa, Niara (Box 173)
        - Swain, Mary Ann (Box 173)
      - Association of American Universities (AAU) (Box 173)
      - Audits, Internal (Box 173)
      - Awards, Miscellaneous (Box 173)
      - Budget
        - General, 3 folders (Box 174)
        - Budget Priorities Committee (BPC) (Box 174)
        - Budget Requests (Box 174)
        - Budget Resources/Needs (Box 174)
        - State Budget Requests (Box 174)
      - Calendar, University (Box 174)
      - Capital Campaign (Box 174)
      - Centers
        - General (Box 174)
        - Continuing Education of Women (CEW) (Box 174)
        - Human Growth and Development (CHGD) (Box 174)
        - Japanese Studies (Box 174)
        - Molecular Genetics (Box 174)
        - Research Libraries (CRL), 4 folders
          - Folder 1 (Box 174)
          - Folders 2-4 (Box 175)
        - Research on Learning and Teaching (CRLT) (Box 175)
      - Child Care Center (Box 175)
      - China (Box 175)
      - Chosun University (Box 175)
      - Commencement (James Shortt) (Box 175)
      - Committee on the Economic Status of the Faculty (CESF) (Box 175)
      - Committee on Ethics, Humanism, and Medicine (Box 175)
      - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (CIC)
        - General, 4 folders (Box 175)
        - Executive Committee (Box 175)
        - University Presidents (Box 175)
      - Computers
        - Computer Networking (Box 176)
        - Computer Policy Committee (Box 176)
        - Interim Assistant (Box 176)
        - Statistical Research Laboratory (Box 176)
      - Computing Budget and Planning (Box 176)
      - Computing Center and Computing
        - General, 3 folders (Box 176)
        - Computing Center Access Task Force (Box 176)
      - Conflict of Interest (Box 176)
      - Congratulatory Letters (Box 176)
      - Counsel, General (Roderick Daane) (Box 176)
      - Counseling Review, Task Force on (Robert Suave) (Box 176)
      - Deans, Chancellors (Box 176)
      - Deans, Directors, Department Heads (memos to) (Box 176)
      - Debt Financing and Capital Renewal (Box 176)
      - Detroit Free Press (Box 176)
      - Development Office (Box 176)
      - Distinguished University Professorships (Box 176)
      - Division of Research Development and Administration (DRDA) (Box 176)
      - Early Retirement (Box 176)
      - Economic Dinner Group (Box 176)
      - Endowed Chair, Professorships Procedures (Box 176)
      - Endowments, Bequests, Trusts (Box 176)
      - Energy Studies Program (Robert Holbrook) (Box 176)
      - Enrollment
        - General (Box 176)
        - Enrollment Planning (Box 176)
        - Minority Enrollment (Box 176)
      - Executive Officers
        - Meetings
          - General, 5 folders (Box 177)
          - Retreat (on Minority Enrollment) (Box 178)
          - Special Meetings (Box 178)
        - Officers
          - President Harold Shapiro (Box 178)
          - Vice Presidents
            - Brinkerhoff, J. F (Box 178)
            - Cosovich, Jon (Box 178)
            - Frye, Billy (includes personal), 2 folders (Box 178)
            - Johnson, Henry (Box 178)
            - Kennedy, R.L (Box 178)
            - Sussman, Al (Box 178)
            - Vice President for Research Search (Box 303)
            - Wilson, Linda (Box 178)
          - Vice Provost for Medical Affairs (George Zuidema) (Box 178)
      - Extension Service (Box 178)
      - Faculty
        - General (Box 178)
        - Faculty Grievance Procedures (Box 178)
        - Faculty Unionization (Box 178)
      - Federal Government (Box 178)
      - Fees and Tuition (Box 178)
      - Financial Aid Office
        - Draft Registration (Box 178)
        - Task Force on Graduate Student Aid (Box 178)
        - Task Force on Undergraduate Student Aid (Box 178)
      - Foundations (Box 179)
      - Gender Studies (Box 179)
      - Government Agencies (Box 179)
      - Graduate Student Assistants (GSA/GEO) (Box 179)
      - Grievances (Box 303)
      - Honorary Degree Committee (Box 179)
      - Hospital
        - General (Box 179)
        - Executive Board (Box 179)
        - Executive Officer Briefing (Box 179)
        - Financing (Box 179)
        - Governance (Box 179)
        - Replacement Hospital Project (Box 179)
        - Reading (Box 179)
      - Housing Office (Henry Johnson) (Box 179)
      - Humanities (Box 179)
      - Humor (Box 179)
      - Indirect Cost Reimbursement (Box 179)
      - Information Technology (Box 179)
      - Information Technology, Vice Provost for (Box 179)
      - Institute for Public Policy Studies (IPPS) (Box 179)
      - Institute for Science and Technology (IST) (Box 180)
      - Institute for Social Research (ISR) (Box 180)
      - Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations (ILIR) (Box 180)
      - Intercollegiate Athletics (Box 180)
      - International
        - Korea-Chosun (Box 180)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 180)
      - Investment and Divestment (Box 180)
      - Invitations (Box 180)
      - K-12/University (Box 180)
      - Libraries
        - Bentley Library (Box 180)
        - Clements Library (Box 180)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 180)
        - University Library
          - General, 2 folders (Box 181)
          - Budget Conference (Box 181)
          - Council on Library Resources, 2 folders (Box 181)
      - Management Incentives (Box 181)
      - MacGregor Fund (Box 181)
      - Medical Center, 3 folders (Box 181)
      - Memberships, University (Box 181)
      - Michigan Media (Box 181)
      - Michigan Molecular Institute (Box 181)
      - Michigan Research Corporation (Box 181)
      - Michigan Technology Council (Box 181)
      - Middle English Dictionary (Box 181)
      - Minorities (Box 181)
      - Minority Retreat (Box 182)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 182)
      - Museum of Art (Box 182)
      - Museums, Conservation Needs of (Box 182)
      - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges (NASULGC)
        - General (Box 182)
        - Executive Committee, 3 folders (Box 182)
      - Nuclear Free Zone (Box 182)
      - Personnel, 2 folders (Box 182)
      - Plant Extension (Box 182)
      - President's Council of State Colleges and Universities (PCSCU) (Box 182)
      - Professional Theatre Program (PTP) (Box 182)
      - Promotion Procedures (Box 183)
      - Promotion Recommendations, 1 folder (Box 303)
      - Proposition C (Box 183)
      - Protein Structure and Design (Box 183)
      - Recommendations (Box 183)
      - Regents
        - Bylaws (Box 183)
        - Correspondence (Box 183)
        - Communications (Box 183)
        - Fellowships (Box 183)
      - Registrar's Office
        - General (Box 183)
        - Search
          - General (Box 304)
          - Report of the Advisory Committee to Assist in the Search for the University Registrar, 1 volume (Box 304)
          - Resumes and Writing Samples of Candidates (Box 304)
      - Requests from Institutions and Individuals (Box 183)
      - Research (miscellaneous and proposals) (Box 183)
      - Research Incentives (Box 183)
      - Reserve Officer Training Corps (ROTC) (Box 183)
      - Retirement Furlough (Box 183)
      - Retreat (August 1984) (Box 183)
      - Retrenchment (Box 183)
      - Salary Equity Study (Box 184)
      - Salary Information, 1 folder (Box 184)
      - Salary Recommendations (Box 304)
      - Scheduling Office (Robert Holmes) (Box 184)
      - Scholarships and Fellowships (Box 184)
      - Scholarship, Integrity of (Box 184)
      - Scientific Club (Box 184)
      - Search Committee Guidelines (Box 184)
      - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA) (Box 184)
      - Senate Assembly (Box 184)
      - Separate Legal Entity (Box 184)
      - Society of Fellows (Box 184)
      - Software Engineering Institute (Box 184)
      - SOUP Group (Box 184)
      - Staff Records Office (Box 184)
      - Students (Box 184)
      - Supercomputers (Box 185)
      - Telecommunications (Box 185)
      - Tenure (Box 185)
      - Tropical Studies, Organization for (OTS) (Box 185)
      - University of Michigan News and Information Services (Box 185)
      - Visits (Box 185)
      - Wayne County General Hospital (Box 185)
      - Women (Box 185)
    - Chronological Files
      - 1984
        - July-December, 6 folders (Box 185)
      - 1985
        - January-March, 3 folders (Box 185)
        - April-May, 2 folders (Box 186)
    - Schools and Colleges Files
      - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of, 2 folders (Box 186)
      - Art, School of, General
        - Budget (Box 186)
        - Dean Search (Box 304)
        - Transition Team (Box 186)
      - Business Administration, School of
        - General, 2 folders (Box 186)
        - Budget (Box 186)
        - Retreat (Box 187)
      - Dearborn Campus (Box 187)
      - Dentistry, School of
        - General (Box 187)
        - Budget (Box 187)
        - Mini-Retreat (Box 187)
      - Education, School of
        - General, 3 folders (Box 187)
        - Budget (Box 187)
        - Centers (Box 187)
        - Transition Team (Box 187)
      - Engineering, College of
        - General, 2 folders (Box 187)
        - Budget, 2 folders (Box 188)
        - Computer and Communications Science (Box 188)
        - Research Center (Box 188)
        - Transportation Research Institute (UMTRI) (Box 188)
      - Flint Campus
        - General (Box 188)
        - Nursing, School of (Box 188)
      - Graduate Studies, Rackham School of
        - General (Box 188)
        - Research Merger (proposed merger of Offices of Vice President for Research and Dean of Rackham) (Box 188)
      - Law, School of
        - General (Box 188)
        - Budget Conference (Box 188)
        - Library (Box 188)
      - Library Science, School of (Box 188)
      - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of
        - Biological Sciences (Box 188)
        - Budget Conference (Box 188)
        - Chemistry
          - General (Box 189)
          - Building (Box 189)
          - Review (Box 189)
        - Classical Studies (Box 189)
        - Coalition for Use of Learning Skills (CULS) (Box 189)
        - Collegiate Institute for Values and Science (CIVS) (Box 189)
        - Cognitive Science Program (Box 189)
        - Dean's Office (Box 189)
        - Economics (Box 189)
        - Endowments (Box 189)
        - English (Box 189)
        - English Composition Board (ECB) (Box 189)
        - Faculty Appointments (Regents' Communications) (Box 189)
        - Geological Sciences (Box 189)
        - Humanities (Box 189)
        - History of Art (Box 189)
        - History (Box 189)
        - Mathematics (Box 189)
        - Miscellaneous Units, 3 folders (Box 189)
        - Museums and Centers (Box 189)
        - Natural Science Building (Box 189)
        - Near Eastern Studies (Box 189)
        - Philosophy (Box 190)
        - Physics
          - General (Box 190)
          - Long-Range Planning (Box 190)
        - Political Science (Box 190)
        - Psychology/Education (Box 190)
        - Sociology (Box 190)
        - Tappan Hall Project (Box 190)
      - Medical School
        - General, 3 folders (Box 190)
        - Alumni Society (Box 190)
        - Basic Science Retreat (Box 190)
        - Biomedical Research (Box 190)
        - Budget Conference (Box 190)
        - Capital Needs (Box 190)
        - Clinical Track (Box 190)
        - "Cost of Health Care-Role and Impact of the Surgeon" (Box 190)
        - Enrollment (Box 190)
        - Faculty Appointments (Regents' Communications) (Box 190)
        - Family Practice, Department of, External Review (Box 190)
        - Inteflex (Box 190)
        - Medical Center Retreat (Box 190)
        - Medical Education Task Force (Box 191)
        - Medical Service Plans (Box 191)
        - Medical Technology Program (Box 191)
        - Pathology, Department of (annual report) (Box 191)
        - Regents Briefing (Box 191)
        - Sports Medicine (Box 191)
        - Taubman Library (Box 191)
        - Threatt, Barbara (re: disposition of research records) (Box 191)
        - Unit for Laboratory Animal Medicine (Box 191)
      - Music, School of
        - General (Box 191)
        - Budget Conference (Box 191)
        - Theater (Box 191)
      - Natural Resources, School of
        - General, 3 folders (Box 191)
        - Budget Conference (Box 191)
        - Reviews (external, internal, accreditation), 5 folders
          - Folders 1-2 (Box 191)
          - Folders 3-5 (Box 192)
      - Nursing, School of
        - General (Box 192)
        - Budget Conference (Box 192)
      - Pharmacy, College of
        - General (Box 192)
        - Budget Conference (Box 192)
      - Physical Education (Box 192)
      - Public Health, School of
        - General (Box 192)
        - Budget (Box 192)
      - Social Work, School of
        - General (Box 192)
        - Budget Conference (Box 192)
  - 1985-1986
    - Alphabetical Files
      - Academic Affairs Advisory Committee (Box 193)
      - Academic Affairs Advisory Council, 3 folders (Box 193)
      - Academic Affairs Brown Bag Meetings (Box 193)
      - Academic Affairs Budget (Box 193)
      - Academic Affairs Policy (Box 193)
      - Academic Affairs Salaries (Box 193)
      - Academic Affairs Staff, 2 folders (Box 193)
      - Academic Freedom (Box 193)
      - Academic Planning and Analysis, Office of (Box 193)
      - Academic Policy Group (APG), 3 folders (Box 193)
      - Academic Service Units (Box 193)
      - Academic Services (Robert Holmes) (Box 193)
      - Admissions
        - General, 3 folders (Box 194)